Bishkek / Kyrgyzstan

□ (+996) 706 20-00-10 | ■ akinmyrza2000@gmail.com | 🗖 /akinmyrza-kanat-uulu-57907a182/

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary.

Currently Frontend Developer at start-up company ManchoDevs. 1+ years experience specializing in the web development, developed and maintained several applications and used latest technologies. Learned how to work with team members and programming principles, responsible for the product. Interested in devising a better problem solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises

Work Experience

Mancho Devs Bishkek, Kyrgyzstan

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Jun. 2021 - Mar. 2022

- Developed web applications for automating processes at customs and logistics terminals.
- Developed a web application where complex production types of equipment are sold.
- Participated to implement several API microservices in Node.js and in the serverless AWS Lambda functions.
- Used latest technologies: Typescript, React, GraphQL, Gatsby, AWS, DynamoDB, RxJs, Redux

ManchoDevs Bishkek, Kyrgyzstan

FRONTEND DEVELOPER INTERNSHIP

Feb. 2021 - Jun. 2021

- Developed and maintained from zero two SPA (single page application) web sites
- · Used latest technologies, Typescript, React, GraphQL

Honors & Awards

INTERNATIONAL

2017 **Honorable Mention**, Genius Olympiad

Oswego, U.S.A

2016 Silver medal, the World Scholar's Cup debate

Almaty, Kazakhstan

DOMESTIC

2017 **Silver medal**, the World Scholar's Cup debate

Bishkek, Kyrgyzstan

2017 **Honorable mention,** Informatics Olympiad

Naryn, Kyrgyzstan

Education

Jusup Balasagyn Kyrgyz State University

Bishkek, Kyrgyzstan

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Feb. 2021 - Current

 Courses: Computer Networks, Relational Database Management, Software Engineering, Microprocessors, Data mining and Object oriented programming.

Ala-Too International University

Bishkek, Kyrgyzstan

Sep. 2018 - Feb. 2020

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

• CGPA: 3.5/4.0

 Courses: Computer Networks, Relational Database Management, Software Engineering, Microprocessors, Data mining and Object oriented programming.

Naryn Kyrgyz-Turkish lyceum

Naryn, Kyrgyzstan

Sep. 2013 - May. 2018

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

- CGPA:5.0/5.0
- Education in English

March 14, 2022 Akinmyrza Kanat uulu · Resume

Language skills_

Kyrgyz Native

English Upper-intermediateRussian Upper-intermediateTurkish IntermediateKazhak Intermediate

Technical skills _____

- Confident PC user. All office programs and applications: MS Office, Word, Excel, PowerPoint. Internet, mail
- Used latest technologies in programming: Typescript, React, GraphQL, Gatsby, AWS, DynamoDB, RxJs, Redux

Additionally _____

• Free time activities / hobbies: Basketball, travel, photography, reading interesting articles